<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="name" translatable="false">Pablo Costa</string>
    <string name="social_profiles_github_text" translatable="false">GitHub</string>
    <string name="social_profiles_github_url" translatable="false">https://github.com/Sottti</string>
    <string name="social_profiles_instagram_text" translatable="false">Instagram</string>
    <string name="social_profiles_instagram_url" translatable="false">https://www.instagram.com/sottti/</string>
    <string name="social_profiles_linked_in_text" translatable="false">LinkedIn</string>
    <string name="social_profiles_linked_in_url" translatable="false">https://www.linkedin.com/in/sotti/</string>
    <string name="social_profiles_medium_text" translatable="false">Medium</string>
    <string name="social_profiles_medium_url" translatable="false">https://medium.com/@sotti</string>
    <string name="social_profiles_stack_overflow_text" translatable="false">SO</string>
    <string name="social_profiles_stack_overflow_url" translatable="false">https://stackoverflow.com/users/1177959/sotti</string>
    <string name="social_profiles_x_text" translatable="false">X</string>
    <string name="social_profiles_x_url" translatable="false">https://x.com/Sotttti</string>
    <string name="topic_android_architecture_description">I recall when the industry consensus shifted, recognizing that consolidating all functionality into a single Activity was not a sustainable architecture. Today, discussions often emphasize that an overabundance of layers and abstractions can similarly introduce challenges. Android architecture has undeniably evolved significantly.\n\nReflecting on the progression through various software design patterns (such as MVP, MVVM, MVC, and MVI), architectural solutions like Clean Architecture, and the SOLID principles, I find it engaging to explore what remains truly relevant and which new paradigms are shaping Android Engineering in its dynamic landscape. \n\nApp modularization stands out as a critical component in this context, though its implementation demands a unique strategy for each project and team, carefully balancing the inherent trade-offs.My practical experience with modularization is extensive, spanning applications from a single module to those exceeding a thousand. I\'ve successfully navigated migrations from monolithic designs to highly modular architectures, and the versatility of modular approaches continues to be a source of fascination. While the full spectrum of modularization benefits isn\'t always immediately apparent, I am a strong advocate for its adoption, given the significant long-term advantages it offers in project maintainability, scalability, and team collaboration.</string>
    <string name="topic_android_architecture_title">Architecture</string>
    <string name="topic_android_design_systems_description">I am deeply passionate about design and design systems, topics I discuss with great enthusiasm. I\'ve had the privilege of contributing to the creation of two design systems from the ground up, which helped me gain valuable experience developing these systems for both the traditional Android View system and Jetpack Compose—a process I found immensely rewarding that goes from finding the right optical balance when creating iconography¹ to full standardized pages. In my view, a robust design system is a cornerstone not only for a successful product but for the entire company.\n\nFurthermore, I enjoy organizing meetups centered on design systems, particularly exploring effective collaboration between design and engineering teams. I have fond memories of the very first meetup I organized at Cuvva, which was dedicated to design.</string>
    <string name="topic_android_design_systems_hyperlink_text" translatable="false">¹Cuvva\'s Design System Icons</string>
    <string name="topic_android_design_systems_hyperlink_url" translatable="false">https://dribbble.com/shots/14257561-Cuvva-s-Design-System-Icons</string>
    <string name="topic_android_design_systems_title">Design Systems</string>
    <string name="topic_android_jetpack_compose_description">I\'ve been an enthusiastic user of Jetpack Compose since its earliest alpha releases in 2020 and have thoroughly enjoyed the development experience it offers. \n\nAt Cuvva, I was responsible for one of the initial production commits incorporating Jetpack Compose in late 2020. Our team subsequently participated in a research program with Google¹ that was showcased at Google I/O 2021. \n\nI\'ve had the pleasure of creating Android Design Systems using both the traditional Android View system and Jetpack Compose. In my view, Jetpack Compose represents a significant advancement for the Android UI toolkit because it strikes an optimal balance between customization, granularity, simplicity, and accelerated development cycles through faster feedback loops. \n\nThe live-updating previews, in particular, were a game-changer for my approach to UI development and design system creation.</string>
    <string name="topic_android_jetpack_compose_hyperlink_text" translatable="false">¹Cuvva builds faster and with higher quality with Compose</string>
    <string name="topic_android_jetpack_compose_hyperlink_url" translatable="false">https://developer.android.com/stories/apps/cuvva-compose</string>
    <string name="topic_android_jetpack_compose_title">Jetpack Compose</string>
    <string name="topic_android_material_design_description">I\'ve been a fan of Material Design since its introduction in 2014, as it was my gateway to understanding Design Systems and UI design principles. \n\nWhile it is commendable that Material Design has evolved to be less opinionated and more agnostic regarding design choices, I sometimes miss the deep dives into its documentation, searching for the ideal component for a use case and collaborating with designers on the optimal way to achieve an excellent design.\n\nI\'ve worked extensively with the original Material Design, Material Design 2, and Material Design 3 (including Material You). Currently, I\'m exploring the Material Design 3 Expressive, and I plan to integrate these advancements into this app as development allows.</string>
    <string name="topic_android_material_design_title">Material Design</string>
    <string name="topic_hobbies_aggressive_inline_description">I started aggressive inline skating when I was 11 years old. Since then, I have returned to it for years at a time during three different periods of my life. I just love it.</string>
    <string name="topic_hobbies_aggressive_inline_title">Aggressive Inline</string>
    <string name="topic_hobbies_bodyboard_description">I fell in love with bodyboarding when I was 7 and practised it a lot during my teenage years. I still try to go bodyboarding a bit each summer, and it feels great.</string>
    <string name="topic_hobbies_bodyboard_title">Bodyboard</string>
    <string name="topic_hobbies_guitar_description">I\'ve been playing the guitar sporadically since I was 20, when I bought my first one, which is still with me.</string>
    <string name="topic_hobbies_guitar_title">Guitar</string>
    <string name="topic_hobbies_travel_description">I love travelling with my family, and especially road tripping. I enjoy meeting people from different cultures and backgrounds, hearing their stories, discovering diverse traditions, and exploring city architecture.</string>
    <string name="topic_hobbies_travel_title">Travel</string>
    <string name="topic_journey_description">My enthusiasm for technology began at an early age. While my initial fascination was with computers generally, it was over a decade later that I discovered Android development, a field that has since become a core professional passion.\n\nMy journey in Android development has been more expansive and rewarding than I could have initially anticipated. I\'ve had the unique opportunity to build Android engineering teams from the ground up twice in my career, experiencing the spectrum from working as a sole developer to leading a team of seven. This path has led me through companies of vastly different scales—from a few-person startup to a 200-person organization, and various sizes in between. I\'ve contributed to applications growing from zero to over a million monthly active users and have seen products transition from pre-revenue stages to a robust financial standing.\n\nThis career has also been geographically diverse, involving living and working in two countries and five different cities. My commitment to staying at the forefront of the field is reflected in my attendance at over thirty Android development conferences across nearly ten countries. These engagements have provided invaluable opportunities to collaborate with, learn from, and share insights with talented individuals from every continent and dozens of nationalities—an immensely enriching aspect of my professional life.\n\nAlongside my dedication to crafting high-quality software, I\'ve also discovered and cultivated a deep passion for design, particularly UI/UX and design systems. Collaborating with designers on building and evolving these systems has been one of the most rewarding experiences of my Android career.\n\nLooking ahead, I am committed to continuous growth and to leveraging my experience to contribute to innovative and impactful Android applications. I look forward to embracing new challenges, exploring emerging technologies, and continuing to champion best practices in both software architecture and design systems to help shape the future of mobile experiences.</string>
    <string name="topic_journey_title">Android Journey</string>
    <string name="topic_languages_english_description">I first learned English at school and have been using it in my work for 11 years. I lived in London for 7 years, where I significantly developed my English skills.\n\nI have also continued my English studies at school and attended several intensive courses in New York and Catalonia, each for several weeks.</string>
    <string name="topic_languages_english_title">English</string>
    <string name="topic_languages_galician_description">Galician is my mother tongue. Galician and Spanish are the official languages in Galicia, where I was born. I learned both from a young age and studied them throughout my schooling.</string>
    <string name="topic_languages_galician_title">Galician</string>
    <string name="topic_languages_portuguese_description">Galician (my mother tongue) and Portuguese are very similar languages. They were the same language centuries ago, a shared history that allows for considerable mutual understanding between speakers of both.</string>
    <string name="topic_languages_portuguese_title">Portuguese</string>
    <string name="topic_languages_spanish_description">Spanish is my mother tongue. Spanish and Galician are the official languages in Galicia, where I was born. I learned both from a young age and studied them throughout my schooling.</string>
    <string name="topic_languages_spanish_title">Spanish</string>
    <string name="topic_not_found">There was an error. We\'ll fix it ASAP.</string>
</resources>